{
    "subject": "resource/Estonia",
    "predicate": "property/ethnicGroups",
    "object": "resource/Belarusians",
    "human_readable": "The ethnic groups in Estonia include Belarusians.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874409437179565,
            "question": "Are Belarusians an ethnic group present in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914792001247406,
            "question": "Besides Belarusians, what other ethnic groups live in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883172869682312,
            "question": "What ethnic groups are found in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8828240036964417,
            "question": "Is there a significant Belarusian population in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8492754697799683,
            "question": "Can you name some of the major ethnic groups in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856053113937378,
            "question": "What is the most common ethnic group in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6495136618614197,
            "question": "Does Estonia have a diverse population in terms of ethnicity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5770737528800964,
            "question": "How many Belarusians live in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5164870023727417,
            "question": "What is the ethnic makeup of Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4714779853820801,
            "question": "What are some cultural influences of different ethnic groups in Estonian society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The ethnic groups in Estonia include Belarusians.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8403_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the ethnic makeup of Estonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8403_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many Belarusians live in Estonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8403_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Estonia have a diverse population in terms of ethnicity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8403_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8403_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple. Specifically, document 2 mentions Belarusians as an ethnic group belonging to the East Slavic group and living in Eastern Europe, with some historians considering the inhabitants of the Belarusian Polesie region as a separate ethnic group. Document 4 also mentions Belarusians as one of the ethnic groups living in Estonia, stating that around 12,171 Belarusians live in Estonia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information mentions that \"There are numerous other ethnic groups in Estonia, the largest being Russians, Ukrainians, Belarusians...\" which supports the statement that Belarusians are among the ethnic groups living in Estonia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}